Welcome!
This section is called providing great customer service.
We just want to take a moment to discuss distractions.
Now when you are working in a customer service oriented business, it doesn't really matter where you are.
Whether you are in a convenient store, if you are in the service industry like I am right now.
If you are in an electronics store, it really doesn't matter.
It is very easy to be distracted.
Now in the office environment where I work, if I am working on a spread sheet for example and a customer walks in, it is very easy to try and finish doing what I was doing before the customer came in.
There are also ringing phones, there are other employees who might need their attention.
It is very difficult to do it sometimes when you have all this coming at you at once.